给
Here you go.
希望你喜欢今天的晚餐与演出
And I hope you enjoyed dinner and the show.
看我假装很喜欢当服务员的演出
The show being me pretending I'm happy as a waitress.
卡洛琳 麦克斯人呢
Caroline, where is Max?
我去18层地狱查看过了 她不在那
And I've already checked the bowels of hell.
我知道我是在哪工作
Yeah, I know where I work.
麦克斯今天会迟到
Max is going to be late today
因为她被卡在地铁上了
'cause she got stuck on the subway.
可是你昨天已经说过
But you said yesterday she was late
她因为被卡在地铁上所以迟到了
because she was stuck on the subway.
不是 我昨天说的应该是她被卡在地铁"下"
No, I believe I said yesterday she got stuck under the subway.
奥列格 帮下忙
Oleg, a little help.
麦克斯吗
Oh, Max?
她今天是被卡在公车上
Today she got stuck on a bus.
你前天就说过这个理由了
And you said that the day before yesterday.
厄尔
Earl?
她被卡在月球与纽约市之间了
She got stuck between the moon and New York City.
我知道听起来很扯 但这是真的
I know it's crazy, but it's true.
抱歉我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
我找不到我家的猫 南希
I couldn't find our cat, Nancy.
而且我被卡在公车上或地铁下了
Also, I was stuck on the bus or under the subway.
如果他们跟你说了别的原因
Unless they told you something different,
那我就是因为那原因
then I was doing that.
拜托 这借口没劲到
Oh, come on. That excuse was less satisfying
比《连环》的结尾还烂
than the end of Serial.
麦克斯 你到底把我当什么
Max, really, what do you take me for?
我知道我不能把你当什么
Well, I know where I can't take you.
当你是大人 带你坐迪士尼乐园的大型游乐设施
On the big rides at Disneyland.
南希还没回家
Nancy still hasn't come home.
我要抓狂了
I'm freaking out.
她是我唯一爱的东西
She's the only thing I love.
随便啦
Whatever.
我曾有过一只猫 他又酷
I had a cat once. He was cool.
又黑 而且床上像春运般热闹
He was black and very sexually active.
等等 那只酷猫说的就是老爷我
Oh, wait, the cool cat I'm talking about was me.
厄尔小心点 到你这年纪 随时有可能"马上风"
Earl, be careful, at your age, you could die having sex.
我知道啊
I know.
姑娘们都不知道我是"绝顶升天"还是真升天
Those ladies don't know whether I'm coming or going.
我觉得南希可能再也不会回来了
I think Nancy might be gone for good.
我只是不敢相信她居然没带我一起走
I just can't believe she didn't take me with her.
我们说好的
We had a deal.
麦克斯 她会来我们公寓的
Max, she'll come back to the apartment,
哪怕她有多不想回到那里
even if she doesn't want to.
像我不就是这样吗
I mean, I always do.
你不担心她 我一点也不意外
I am not surprised you're not worried.
你从来就没喜欢过南希
You never really liked Nancy.
你总叫她"那只猫"
You call her "That cat."
比如 "那只猫"尿在我枕头上了
As in, "That cat" peed on my pillow.
当时我还睡在枕头上呢 麦克斯
While I was sleeping on it, Max.
你怪我吧 是我害她喝醉乱尿的
Well, blame me. I got her drunk.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
姑娘们 你们的猫[逼]在我包里
Look, girls, I got your pussy in my purse.
她这句可能是说猫
Either that's a cat,
也或者是你俩得更小心收好自己的"东西"了
or you two got to keep better track of your belongings.
太好了
Yay!
那只猫回来了
That cat's back.
你看 麦克斯
See, Max?
我很兴奋啊
I am excited.
我好想你哦
Oh, I missed you so much.
真的好想你
Oh, yes, I did.
那不是南希
That's not Nancy.
这只是公的
That is a boy.
抱歉麦克斯 我不会猫刚进门
Well, Max, sorry I don't check out a cat's junk
就盯着人家的鸡鸡看
the second it comes through the door.
是啊 你只会看脸
Yeah, you only look at the face.
这就是我们俩的不同
That's the difference between you and me.
你看 名牌上写的是"小桂子"
See, look, the name tag says "Cinnamon."
难怪那个小姑娘边哭边喊着
No wonder that little girl kept crying and saying,
"给我小桂子[肉桂] 给我小桂子"
"Give me Cinnamon, Give me Cinnamon."
我看着她眼睛对她说
I looked her right in the eye and I said,
"我的包里不带香料好吗"
"I don't carry spices in my purse."
麦克斯 你完全反应过度了
Max, you are completely overreacting.
-只是一只... -你说啊 只是什么
- It's just a-- - Oh! Just a what?
说啊
Say it!
只是只猫
It's just a cat.
好你的
You!
是我出的那一块钱来帮她买名牌的好吗
Hey, I'm the one who fronted us that dollar to get her name tag.
多亏我 有人捡到她时
Thanks to me, someone's gonna pick her up,
就会把她举起来说 "哇 你一定是走丢了
look at it, and say, "Oh, you must be lost,
小... 喵喵"
little...cat."
南希 她的名字叫南希
Nancy! Her name's Nancy!
我知道她名字好吗
I know her name!
只是那名字暂时被推出我的脑袋
It got momentarily pushed out of my head
来腾空间给那1600件我们付不起
to make room for those 1,600 cupcake T-shirts
也没地放的小蛋糕T恤
we can't unload or pay for.
我就没有一周有四五个晚上
You think I don't wake up screaming
都做T恤恶梦尖叫着醒来吗
four or five nights a week about those T-shirts?
可我知道我们家猫的名字
But I know our cat's name.
你晚上从来都没醒过好吗
You don't wake up at night ever.
的确 我唯一的天赋技能就是睡得比死婴还沉
No, I sleep like a dead baby, it's my one gift.
电话响了
Oh, the phone!
未知号码 可能就是这个
Unknown number. This could be it!
我喜欢号码像保险套的过期日那样 "未知"
I like my numbers like my condom expiration dates, unknown.
你好
Hello?
-是的 -谁啊 麦克斯
- Yes? - Who is it, Max?
她在你那里吗 太好了
You have her? Yay!
没问题 好的 谢谢
Oh, sure, great. Thank you.
南希在他那边吗
He has her? He has Nancy?
为时已晚 多说无益
Please, too little, too late.
麦克斯 我们欠了一万的债
Max, we're in $10,000 worth of debt
而你还花钱去买新猫砂吗
and you spent money on new kitty litter?
放轻松好吗 我也会在里面尿啊
Relax, I'm going to pee in it, too.
这也的确比你房间里
Well, I guess it beats that Sprite bottle
被你拿来当夜壶的雪碧瓶子强
you've been using in your bedroom.
每次我想起身去厕所
It's just such a long walk to the bathroom
感觉都要跋山涉水
that every time I have to go,
好像我在为多发性硬化症募款一样
it's like I'm raising money for MS.
我有个好消息
Oh, I have good news.
我在猫砂盆里找到你丢了的胸罩
I found your lost bra in the litter box.
我不会因此不穿它啊
Don't think I'm not still wearing it.
我有何好不穿的
I mean, why not?
有次我还吃了一根滚到车底的热狗呢
I ate a hot dog that rolled under a car the other day.
我留了几块大的猫屎尿块
I left a couple of big clumps in,
就当帮你"撑撑场面"
just to help you out a little.
好了 是南希回来了
Oh, okay, that's Nancy.
这是个让你们重新开始的机会
Here's a chance for a fresh start for you two.
记得别提胸罩的事 我们不知道她为啥想要
And don't bring up the bra, we don't know why she wanted it,
但我确定她有她的理由
but I'm sure she had her reasons.
行吧 我会拿出最好的表现
Fine, I'll be on my best behavior.
但你自己睁大眼看看她对我是什么态度
But you watch and see how she treats me.
一个巴掌拍不响好吗
It's a two-way street.
你好 你的猫在我手里
Hi, I have your cat.
而更惊奇的是 你的门把也在我手里
And surprisingly, your doorknob.
那个口香糖这么快就不粘啦
Oh, that gum wore out already?
小家伙
Hi, buddy!
你好 我叫卡洛琳 她是麦克斯
Hi, I'm Caroline. This is Max.
感谢你送回来我们的...
Thank you so much for bringing back--
-南希 我知道
- Nancy! - I know!
而且你搞清楚 她连看都不看我一眼
And please note, she did not even look at me.
你好 我叫欧文
Hi. I'm Owen.
偶们[欧文]欠你个大人情哦
Well, we are "Owen" you a big thank-you.
手头现金有点吃紧 你觉得
Kind of low on cash, how would you feel
一千件小蛋糕T恤怎么样呢
about 1,000 cute cupcake tees?
我不需要一千件粉红T恤
Yeah, I don't need 1,000 pink T-shirts.
我对运动不感兴趣已经够让我爸不爽了
My dad's already mad at me I don't care about sports.
这东西要怎么打开
How do you get this thing open?
我们平常都是把南希放在
We usually just take Nancy around
旧的吸尘器集尘袋里
in an old vacuum cleaner bag.
外兼我的"外出"包包
Also doubles as my "going out" purse.
失礼了 我能进来吗
Pardon me, may I get past?
礼仪
Oh, manners.
出现在我们的门口吗
In our doorway?
我都不知道该怎么做了
I don't know what to do.
接下来呢 前门台阶没有被乱丢的毒品针头吗
What's next, a front stoop with no discarded heroin needles?
我刚从那里上来
Yeah, I just came up there.
看来今天没有
Not today.
来 我来帮你
Here, let me help.
我才是那个花两千块买宠物拎包的傻子
I mean, I'm the dumb one who paid $2,000 for a cat carrier.
我好想念当那种傻子的时光
Hmm. I miss being that stupid.
我的猫也打不开这东西
You know, my cat can't get this open either.
我猜可能是因为没有拇指吧
It must be the lack of thumbs.
有钱 幽默 早上九点就穿着西装
Rich, funny, and in a suit at 9:00 A.M.?
我真的不知道该怎么办了
I really don't know what to do.
其实我的猫狄更斯 很喜欢你家猫
You know, my cat, Dickens, loves your cat.
狄更斯 跟那个作家同名吗
Oh, Dickens, after the author?
是跟作者同名 不是"弟更湿"呢
Dickens, after the author, Max.
我知道他是谁好吗
Yeah, I know who that is.
写《大青蛙布偶秀圣诞颂歌》的那个人嘛
The guy who wrote Muppets Christmas Carol.
来 我就知道我能打开
There. I knew I'd get it.
因为我有拇指
'Cause I have thumbs.
小姑娘你在这呀
Oh, there she is.
从你养猫来看 我猜你单身
So I take it by the cat, you're single?
单到爆
Big time.
那你跟狄更斯是独居吗
So, do you and Dickens live alone?
惨了 她要跟人调情了
Oh no, she's trying to flirt.
我因为工作关系 常到处去
I travel a lot for work.
我是个风险投资人
I'm a venture capitalist.
你懂是怎么样的
So you know how it is.
我懂 我太懂了
Oh, I do. I absolutely do.
-我... -要来了
- I... - Here it comes.
-以前在沃顿读书 -看吧
- Went to Wharton. - Boom.
如果她又丢了 你知道上哪找她
Well, if she gets lost again, you know where to find her.
她过去几个月
She's been hanging around outside our window
天天都在在我家窗外晃悠
every day for the last couple of months.
所以我让她进门了 希望你们不介意
So I let her in. I hope that's okay.
问我介不介意 当然是没问题啦
Is that okay? It's awesome.
只希望你的女朋友不会介意啊
I hope your girlfriend didn't mind.
我们刚分手
We just broke up.
所以我现在是单身
So I'm single.
我最好赶紧撤了
And I better get going.
我十点钟有个会议
I've got a 10:00 meeting.
麦克斯 把宠物拎包还人家
Max, give the man his case.
他十点有个会议呢
He has a 10:00 meeting.
她不想离开这个舒服的东西
She doesn't want to get out of cushy this thing.
我完全懂她心情
I totally get it.
我有一次坐到商场里的按摩椅上
I had to be dragged out of that massage chair
最后也得是保安把我拉下来
at Brookstone by mall security.
这是我的名片 你们要还包时
Well, here's my card, just give me a call
打给我 我会来取
when you want me to pick up the case.
你有名片吗
You have a card?
名片 会议 西装 笑话
A card, a meeting, a suit, a joke?
你是下一个要上《黄金单身汉》的人吗
Are you the next Bachelor?
谢谢你 欧文·查尔斯·博伊得
Well, thank you, Owen Charles Boyd,
带回我们亲爱的...
for bringing back our beloved--
-她的名字叫南希 -我知道她名字
- Her name's Nancy! - I know her name.
我为什么就一定要很快速念出来
Why do I have to say it so fast?
她是在开玩笑 只是她没你这么好笑
She's joking, she's just not as funny as you.
好吧 很高兴认识你
Well, it was nice to meet you.
再见啦 南希
Bye, Nancy.
好吧
Okay.
是的 我的确是在调情
Yes, I was flirting.
但我是为了我们的生意啊
But I was doing it for our business.
你真的应该为你下面的"生意"而调情
You should really be doing it for your business.
因为你的"生意"就快关门大吉了
'Cause your business is going out of business.
他有张名片[卡]
He has a card.
而且不是医用大麻的卡
And it's not for medical marijuana.
他是个风险投资人
He's a venture capitalist.
这种待宰肥猫
That's the kind of fat cat
正是能让我们生意重回正轨的人
that can help us get back on our feet.
说到肥猫 南希看起来
Speaking of fat cats, Nancy's looking like
像是需要给肥珍打个电话了
she might need to give Jenny a call.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
你们找到南希啦
Oh, you found Nancy.
我就知道她会大着肚子回来
I knew she'd come back pregnant.
等等 苏菲 你怎么知道她怀孕了
Wait, Sophie, how can you tell she's pregnant
而不是只是跟小胖仔乔纳·希尔有一样的问题
and just not fighting the same battle Jonah Hill is fighting?
她毛厚了 眼里也多出了些光芒
Well, her fur is thicker, she's got a little sparkle in her eye,
而且小猫的头都要从她洞里探出来了
and there's a little kitten head about to pop out of her patoot.
加油 用力 南希
Come on. Push, Nancy.
我们都知道你干了什么好事
Come on, we all know what you did.
现在不是你害羞的时间
Now is not the time to be shy.
苏菲 你是真懂你在做的这件事吧
You do know what you're doing, right, Sophie?
而不是像你上次跟我们说
This isn't like the time you told us
你知道怎么用蜡烛来做私处除毛一样
you could do your own bikini wax with a candle?
因为那香草味蜡油疤还没消呢
'Cause I still have the vanilla-scented scars from that.
不用担心
Don't worry.
在我老家村里 科臣斯基家的女人
In my village, all the Kuchenskis women
都得当动物的产婆
acted as animal midwives.
这也是认识男人最好的方法了
It was the best way to meet guys.
屏息以待 姑娘们
Strap in, girls.
小猫的头要出来了
She's crowning!
我真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
我一直以为南希没这么傻
I thought Nancy was smarter than this.
但结果发现 她跟我家族里的其他女人
But it turns out she's just like the rest of the women
没啥不同
in my family.
都是被垃圾堆认识的陌生人给搞了
Screwed by some stranger she met in the dumpster.
好了 来啦
Okay, here we go.
我的戒指再见了
Oh, there goes my ring.
抱歉啊 南希
I--sorry, Nancy.
来啦
Oh, here we go!
快点 姑娘们 我需要热水跟干净的毛巾
Come on, girls, I need some hot water and fresh towels.
我们也需要啊 等了有四年了
We do, too. For, like, four years.
这些T恤拿去用怎么样
How about some of these T-shirts?
是啊 干嘛不用呢
Oh, sure why not use those?
它们曾经代表着我们的美好未来
They used to be our bright future.
现在成了私生猫的超吸水毛巾了
Now just a ShamWow for illegitimate cats.
天啊 这大概就是猫子宫缴械投降的声音吧
Oh, my God, that must be the sound of a surrendering cat uterus.
这是好久以来那张床上
Well, it's the first time a uterus has surrendered
第一次有子宫缴械投降吧
in that bed in a while.
我不知道我为什么看到不会想吐
I don't know why I'm not throwing up.
等等 吐意上来了
Oh, wait. I'm starting to.
我这辈子再也不敢直视韩式饺子了
Well, I'm off Korean dumplings for life.
这只 这只不愿意出来[出柜]
This one-- this one won't come out.
就像猫界的奎因·莱提法
It's like the Queen Latifah of kittens.
苏菲 我收到你的短信说你跟南希在床上
Sophie, I got your text that you were in bed with Nancy.
谁是南希
Who is this Nancy,
我们什么时候回去搞三人行
and when did we go back to doing three-ways?
南希是只猫
Nancy's a cat.
这我不行
Mm, that's a no.
没节操也得有个底线吧
I've got to draw the line somewhere.
我听说了
Well, I heard the news.
你们俩没到30岁就当上外婆了
Looks like you two are grandmothers before you're 30.
我一点也不意外
Can't say I'm surprised.
行了 不用问了
Okay, before you even ask,
你们没有带薪陪猫产假
I don't pay for cat maternity leave.
这里又不是谷歌公司
This isn't Google.
这里连金点子公司都算不上 阿憨
This isn't even Ask Jeeves, Han.
我可以帮你们为小猫找到好的领养家庭
Well, I can help you get the kittens good homes.
我楼里的人们都非常友好
The people in my building are very nice.
除非你忘了回收一个苹果气泡酒的瓶子
Except if you don't recycle one bottle of sparkling cider,
那坐电梯的时候就没人鸟你了
then nobody talks to you in the elevator.
阿憨 我们不会把小猫送走
Han, we're not giving the kittens away.
南希傍上了一只有钱猫
Nancy landed herself a rich cat,
我们以后就靠丰厚的小猫抚养费过活啦
we're gonna be living off a hefty kitty support.
这种事只有你们俩才做得出来
Only you two would be desperate enough
跑去找一只干爹猫
to try and find a sugar catty.
欧文有回你电话吗
So has Owen called you back yet?
我们还在约
Um, we're trading.
"我们还在约"
"We're trading"?
寂寞白妞才会打这种官腔
"We're trading" is lonely white girl talk
意思是"他没有回我电话"
for "he hasn't called me back."
真是不敢相信 他是一个不负责任的老爹
I can't believe this. He's a deadbeat dad.
麦克斯 他只是很忙
Max, he's just busy.
我想你可能因为你爸 所以觉得天下乌鸦一般黑
And I think you might be projecting a little because of your dad.
并不是说我是心理医生
Not that I'm a therapist.
拜托 我连给病人坐的沙发都买不起
I mean, I can't even afford a couch.
我才没有呢
I'm not projecting.
一般见不着鬼影的都是不负责任的老爹
I just know a deadbeat dad when I don't see one!
他的名片在哪里
Where's his card?
我不记得我放哪里了
I don't remember where I--
麦克斯 放手 我能搞定
Max, let go! I've got this.
那个家伙真的能帮我们的生意一把
That guy can really help us with our business.
拜托 让我处理吧
Please, let me handle this.
快看 帅气高司令来了
Look, Ryan Gosling.
-我来 -我来
- I got this. - I got this.
继续 姑娘们 我快"来"了
Keep going, girls, I'm almost there.
我来 麦克斯
I got this, Max.
等他过来拿宠物拎包时
And when he comes to get the cat carrier,
我会跟他谈
I'll talk to him.
你现在太激动了
You're way too emotional.
刚才都跟我的围裙到第三垒了
You just went to third base with my apron.
在前门楼梯坐着感觉挺好
Sitting on this stoop is nice.
为什么我们从来不出来坐呢
How come we never sit out here?
这就是原因
There it is.
拜托 那是里克啦
Oh, please, it's just Rico.
里克看起来挺好 好像多了一个纹身
Rico looks good. I think he got another tattoo.
听着 当欧文来了 我们应该还活着
Look, when Owen gets here, should we still be alive,
拜托让我跟他谈
please let me do the talking.
撇开小猫不说 欧文能帮我们
Kittens aside, Owen can help us.
风险投资人专门买公司
A venture capitalist buys companies
然后让它们起死回生
and turns them around.
知道 我看过《风月俏佳人》
Yeah, I've seen Pretty Woman.
那令我意识到我当时要价太少了
That's how I realized I wasn't charging enough.
快走 麦克斯 他来了
Go, Max, here he comes.
好啦 但我会从里面的窗户监视你
All right, but I'll be watching inside from the window.
这样或许更好
It's probably better,
因为我不放心让南希单独和小猫们一起
because I don't trust Nancy alone with those kittens.
她有严重的产后抑郁
She's got some serious postpartum.
当我离开房间时 她用颤抖的猫爪
When I left the room, she was lighting a Menthol 100
点了一根薄荷烟
with a shaky paw.
你好啊
Hi.
咱俩原来住得这么近啊 走路就能到
Crazy we live walking distance from each other.
并没有
We don't.
出租豪车司机不愿意开过拐角那个消防栓
The Uber driver wouldn't go past the fire hydrant on the corner.
那个挂有一只血鞋子的消防栓吗
The one with the bloody shoe hanging from it?
就是那个
That's the one.
算了 我还是拿了宠物包快走吧
You know what? I'm just gonna take the cat carrier.
先等等
Before you go...
我们有一家小蛋糕店
we have this small cupcake company
祈求成为小蛋糕帝国
that's just begging to be an empire,
我想向你讨教一些生意上的事情
and I wanted to pick your brain about some business stuff.
好吧 你的狄更斯把我们的猫肚子搞大了
Okay, so your Dickens got our cat pregnant,
她刚生下了五只小猫
and she just had five kittens.
以她的年纪 我们不用花钱去做试管真是奇迹啊
And at her age, it's a miracle we didn't have to pay for in vitro.
你怎么知道就是狄更斯的
How do you know they are Dickens's?
我不是说南希放荡
I'm not saying that Nancy's easy,
只是我见过她在很多窗户进进出出
it's just, I've seen her go in and out of a lot of windows.
他刚是掉了一把枪吗
Did he just drop a gun?
没关系 他还有更多
It's fine. He has more.
好吧 给我助理打电话 你可以向我讨教[大脑]
Okay, call my assistant, you can pick my brain.
我不想它[脑浆]飞溅出人行道
I just don't want it to be off the sidewalk.
我真的得走了 我不能丧命
Really, I got to go. I can't get killed.
我穿着新的麂皮乐福鞋呢
I'm wearing new suede loafers.
豪车 助理还有麂皮乐福鞋
Uber, an assistant, and suede loafers?
我不是在做梦吧
Are you for real?
希望我没有打扰你
I hope I'm not intruding.
没有 进来吧
No, come in.
我在刷我的新乐福鞋呢
I was just brushing my new loafers.
这是我为自己买的分手礼物
I bought them as a break-up gift for myself.
不像我前女友 鞋子有底 她节操无底
But unlike my ex-girlfriend, these have a sole.
我不想跟你的助理提猫的事情
I didn't wanna mention the cat situation to your assistant.
不然很快这件事就会被传得人尽皆知
Next thing you know, it's all over the lunch room:
欧文·查尔斯·博伊德的猫爱到处留种
Owen Charles Boyd's cat is a raw-dogger.
我的商业伙伴踩到我的鞋子
My business partner stepped on them.
说是不小心的
Said it was an accident.
但我觉得不像
Didn't feel like one.
踩一只还有可能 但两只的话
One shoe yes, but both?
相当不可能
Highly unlikely.
欧文 有时在生活中
Owen, sometimes in life,
不光只有无辜的猫会被搞惨
it's not just an innocent cat that gets screwed.
女人也会被人搞得惨兮兮
A girl can get screwed as well.
你好 请问现在是什么情况
Oh, hey, hi. What's happening?
我是说错误的商业决定而被搞惨
As in, screwed by one bad business decision.
我和我的合伙人麦克斯 最近把我们所有的钱投在
My partner, Max, and I recently invested all our savings in--
给 你看看
well, here, take a look.
我的咖啡
Oh, my coffee!
我的乐福鞋
My loafer!
我的咖啡洒我的乐福鞋上了
My coffee's on my loafer!
让我来吧
Here, let me.
不 要轻拭 麂皮不能摩擦
No, you dab. You don't wipe suede.
要轻轻拍打
You dab.
轻拍 轻拍 抱歉
Dab. Dab. I'm sorry.
我以前知道这点
I used to know that.
那可是富人的基本常识
That's Rich 101.
我去找点水
Let me just go find some water
然后我会轻拭干净 绝不用力擦
and I'll dab, not wipe, this out.
我们还没说完 我晚点再进去
We're not done yet. I'm going back in.
我们的谈话进展得非常顺利
It's going really well though.
水在哪里
Where's water?
你知道怎么撤回邮件吗
Do you know how to unsend an email?
如果我懂 我富豪前男友绝不会发现
If I did, my rich ex-boyfriend would've never found out
我对他口齿不清的看法
what I thought of his lisp
那现在我就会住在"花国兰部"[法国南部]了
and I'd be living in the "Thouth of Franth" right now.
他在哪里
Where is he?
他得看看这些可爱的小王八蛋
He needs to see these adorable bastards.
麦克斯 你怎么知道我在这里
Max, how did you find me here?
我明明告诉你我去散个"思考之步"
I told you I was going on a "think walk."
我跟踪你了
I followed you.
我从没发现到你有多常把商店橱窗当镜子照
I never noticed how much you check yourself out in store windows.
你有病得治
You have a problem.
你们俩谁知道怎么把
Do either of you know a way to turn the phrase,
"自恋可笑的猪头"变成称赞人的话吗
"Self-absorbed, ridiculous pig" into a compliment?
如果我懂 那我现在还在录《学徒》呢
If I did, I'd still be on The Apprentice.
欧文会看见那封邮件
Owen's going to see that email
我要被炒鱿鱼了
and I'm going to get fired.
我以后得开始注重细节才行了
I have to start paying attention to details.
我要进去了
I'm just gonna go back in.
随便 我不在乎
What? I don't care.
想进去就得带我一起
Not without me you're not.
麦克斯 拜托 让我处理这件事吧
Max, please, let me handle this.
求你了
I'm begging you.
我们很接近了 瞧 我都拿着他的鞋了
We're getting close, look, I'm holding his shoe.
如果他不站出来
If he doesn't step up here,
这些小猫会觉得被忽视
these kittens will feel neglected,
他们以后当服务员或更糟只是迟早的事
and it is only a matter of time till they are waitressing or worse.
麦克斯 你错了
Max, you're wrong.
世上没有比当服务员更糟的事情了
There's nothing worse than waitressing.
麦克斯 停下
Max, stop!
你会毁了一切
You'll ruin everything.
我可以解决这件事 拯救我们
I can fix this and us.
我们已经回天乏术了
We are beyond help.
现在的重点是这些小猫
It's all about these kittens.
-走开 让我来 -不 我来
- Now move, I got this. - No, I got this.
-我来 -我来
- I got this. - I got this.
我...
I--
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
这到底是怎么回事
What the hell is happening?
没错 我带着一篮子猫来你的办公室
That's right. I came to your office with a basket of cats.
麦克斯 很抱歉
Max, I'm so sorry.
是啊 他才是那个应该觉得抱歉的人
Yeah, well, he's the one who should be sorry.
我要你看着这些小猫的胡子
I want you to look these kittens in the whiskers
告诉他们狄更斯不是他们的父亲
and tell them that Dickens is not their father.
你凭什么认为它们是我的 为什么
What makes you think they're mine. Why?
就因为它们长得跟狄更斯
Because they look just like Dickens
小时候一模一样吗
when he was a tiny baby kitten.
这只显然更可爱
Oh, and this one's even cuter.
还有那只
And that one.
我全部都要了
I'll take them all.
但不要那只 它看起有点不在状态
But not that one. Seems a little off.
不如其他几只看着机灵
Not quite as alert as the others.
她不够好 配不上你吗
Oh, she's not good enough for you?
-麦克斯 你又来了 -我没有
- Max. Projecting. - I'm not projecting.
他说她不好配不上他
He said she's not good enough for him.
什么
What?
就因为她是意外怀上的 还不擅长数学吗
Just because she was unplanned and not good at math?
胸部发育得太早吗
Developed boobs way too early?
好吧 我的确是情感投射转移了
Okay, fine. I'm projecting.
怎么回事
What is going on?
卡洛琳 你是要勾搭我吗
Caroline, are we gonna hook up or what?
现在的情况就像最诡异的前戏
This is, like the weirdest foreplay ever.
勾搭 你凭什么认为我想勾搭你
Hook up? What would make you think I want to hook up?
因为我的商业调情吗
Oh, because I business flirted?
那可是沃顿的基础课
That's Wharton 101.
这岂止是商业调情这么简单
It was more than business flirting.
你求着要来我的办公室
You begged to come to my office,
穿着透视装来
show up wearing a see-through shirt.
不是我想它能透视
That was not by choice.
是它质量太差料子薄
It is cheaply made.
我来是为了跟你谈我们的生意
I came here to talk to you about our business,
期望你可能会投资我们这个麻雀虽小 但...
and possibly get you to invest in a small, but spirited--
投资吗 这里可是世界的金融首都
Invest? This is the financial capital of the world.
是的哟
Yes, it is.
我为什么要投资一家走投无路的小蛋糕店
Why would I invest in a desperate little cupcake shop?
好你的
You!
够了
That's it!
喵星人不给你了
No cats for you.
你知道吗
You know what?
你是个自恋可笑的猪头
You are a self-absorbed, ridiculous pig.
你胡扯
Says you.
你秘书也这么说
And your assistant.
去看看你的电邮吧
Check your email.
我成功撤回信件了
I was able to unsend it.
你的商业人际网资料可以更新一下了
Yeah, might want to re-ignite that LinkedIn profile.
你之后可能会有很多时间在家 想要只猫吗
You're gonna be home a lot more, you want a cat?
谢谢你收下这些猫 阿憨
Thanks for taking the kittens, Han.
我觉得你特别理解小东西
I feel like you have an understanding
毕竟你自己也是其中一员
of small creatures, being one yourself.
不用担心 我搂里住了一堆拉拉
Have no fear, my building is loaded with lesbians.
她们抢流浪猫的速度
They take home rescue cats
会比她们带别的拉拉回家速度还快
faster than they take home other lesbians.
先谈谈我的要求
Okay, let's discuss my terms.
跟我非动物类的孩子不同
Unlike all my non-animal children,
我想要知道它们有被妥善照料
I want to know they're taken care of.
拉拉你还不懂吗
What part of lesbian don't you understand?
在今晚之前它们就会被法兰绒的襁褓里了
They'll be swaddled in a flannel shirt by nightfall.
这只我叫他小毒虫
Okay, now this one, I call Junkie.
因为他对猫薄荷[猫毒品]强烈上瘾
'Cause he's got a serious Catnip problem.
所以你在一周内就培养出了个瘾君子
Oh, so you raised a drug addict within a week.
听起来就像你会干的事
Sounds about right.
这两只应该尽量让同一个人收养
These two should try and stay together.
我们叫他们"权力的游戏一号"
We call them Game of Thrones One
与"权利的游戏二号"
and Game of Thrones Two.
因为他们是亲人也是爱人[剧中有乱伦]
'Cause they're siblings and lovers.
这只是个男孩
This one's the boy.
你多看看他 跟他学学怎么"推屁股"
Watch him and learn what humping looks like.
这只比较闷
This one's pretty bland.
她喜欢趴着 不怎么喵喵叫
She lays around, doesn't meow much,
就算真叫了 也不是太认真
and when she does, she's kind of phoning it in.
所以我们叫她艾米·亚当斯
We call her Amy Adams.
是的
Yep.
最后这只最受我们注意
This last one gets special attention.
她最小只 但很有潜力
She's the smallest, but she's got potential.
你看看她的乳头
I mean, look at those nipples.
现在我满脑子都是乳头
And now the nipples are all I see.
祝你们有美好的猫生
Have a nice life.
我会上照片分享网找你们
I'll find you on Instagram.
记得去看看网红暴躁猫
Check out Grumpy Cat.
多学学他
Do what he does.
再见啦 小猫们
Well, bye, kitties.
记得 跳脱衣舞不算是跳舞
And remember, stripping isn't dancing.
现在我满脑子都是它们贴着乳头贴
And now all I can see is them wearing pasties.
麦克斯 你知道吗
You know what, Max?
我们不需要那个有钱人来拯救我们的生意
We don't need that rich guy to fix our business.
我们可以自己拯救
We can do it ourselves.
我骗谁啊 我们生意的状态
Who am I kidding? Our business is in worse shape
比两个退休后打高球的老头体态还差
than two retired guys in a golf cart.
你知道我们更应该拯救什么吗
Well, you know what we'd better fix?
南希
Nancy.
因为有钱仔说的没错 她真是个浪货
'Cause he was right, she's a slut.
有人在小巷里发现她跟一只虎斑猫在69
Someone just found her 69-ing a tabby in the alley.